{"data":[{"question":"Until recently, photocopy machines were regarded strict as business and professional office equipment that required a lot of expensive servicing.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Until","b":"were regarded","c":"strict as","d":"that required","answer":"3","explain":" - Strict as-> strictly as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Before bridges were built, all transport across major rivers in the United States were by ferryboat.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"bridges","b":"were built","c":"were","d":"by","answer":"3","explain":" - Were-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Telling a story through letters was a narratively structure commonly used by eighteenth-century novelists.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Telling a story","b":"narratively structure","c":"commonly used","d":"eighteenth-century novelists","answer":"2","explain":" - Narratively structure -> Narrative structure","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"People in the world differ in his beliefs about the cause of sickness and health.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"differ","b":"his","c":"about","d":"and","answer":"2","explain":" - His-> their","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"In the 1840s, hundreds of families pioneer moved west in their covered wagons.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In the","b":"hundreds","c":"families pioneer","d":"their","answer":"3","explain":" - Families pioneer-> pioneer families","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"When children get their first pair of glasses, they are often surprise to see that trees and flowers have sharp clear outlines.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"pair","c":"surprise","d":"have","answer":"3","explain":" - Supprise-> supprised","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"The indiscriminate and continual use of any drug without medical supervision can be danger.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"use of","b":"without","c":"medical","d":"danger","answer":"4","explain":" - Danger-> dangerous","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"In 1931 Jane Adams was a Nobel Peace Prize recipient for she humanitarian achievements.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"was","c":"she","d":"achievements","answer":"3","explain":" - She-> her","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Even on the most careful prepared trip, problems will sometimes develop.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Even","b":"careful","c":"trip","d":"will sometimes","answer":"2","explain":" - Careful-> carefully","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Many people say that California is a state of geographic remarkable diversity.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Many","b":"a state","c":"geographic remarkable","d":"diversity","answer":"3","explain":" - Geographic remarkable -> Remarkably geographic","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"}]}